ABOUT ME

My name is Jarosław Janas and I'm a Front-End Developer. I started my work with code in 2020. I really enjoy it and I want to be a better Web-Developer every day. My specialization is creating websites and applications in JavaScript language.

EXPERIENCE

2019 - NOW



Hotel Receptionist – Aparthotel Miodowa

Cracow

checking reservations, service for hotel guests, taking care of the positive image of the hotel

2018 - 2018



Soldier of Polish Army – 22nd Mountain Infantry Battalion,

Kłodzko

military service for the country, improvement in: strategy, military leadership, shooting, rescue and defense against weapons of mass destruction

2017 - 2018



Hostel Menager - Heynow Hostel

Cracow

hostel administrations, marketing, recruitment and management of new employees, operating reservation systems, taking care of the positive image of the hostel

EDUCATION

2020 - NOW



Front-End Developer – Courses on the UDEMY e-learning platform

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT

2017 - 2019



Master Degree – Pedagogical University of Cracow

education for security and crisis management

2014 - 2017



Bachelor Degree – Pedagogical University of Cracow

national security



Jarosław Janas

CONTACT



+48 798 194 305



jarekjanas95@gmail.com



www.jarek-portfolio.netlify.app



Cracow 31-222, Poland

SKILLS

Professional:



HTML



CSS



JAVASCRIPT



REACT

Personal:

- CREATIVITY
- SELF-MOTIVATION
- TEAM WORK
- SCRUPULOUSNESS

Languages:

- POLISH
- ENGLISH